OGUNLALA ADEDAMOLA COLLINS

5, Adewale Street, Coker-Surulere,

6th March, 1997

Lagos, Nigeria.

26 years

collinsogunlala@gmail.com

08174726892

Professional Summary

Motivated self-starter and creative problem solver who works hard and enjoys a challenge. Outstanding problem-solving, planning, and organizational abilities. Practical experience with microbial cultures, preparation, and routine microbiological laboratory techniques. Strong understanding of standard laboratory methods.

Skills

- Equipment Handling Research & Reporting
- Web Services
- Problem Solving abilities

- Test Methods
- Computer Proficiency
- Communication Skill

Experience

AIICO Insurance PLC

Plot 2, Oba Akran Avenue, Ikeja, Lagos, Nigeria

Underwriter (Retail Processing Unit)

Jan, 2023 - Current

- Collaborating with insurance agents, brokers, and other professionals to ensure that policies or financial offerings meet the needs of clients.
- Providing recommendations and guidance to clients on risk management and insurance options, based on their specific needs and circumstances.
- Reviewing the terms and conditions of policies or financial offerings to determine whether the risks associated with them can be accepted and insured.

nTells Computer Training Center

Lagos, Nigeria.

Front End Developer

May, 2022 - Jan, 2023

- Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages
- Maintaining and improving websites
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Get feedback from, and build solutions for, users and customers
- Create quality mockups and prototypes
- Stay up-to-date on emerging technologies

Azager Shopping

Lagos, Nigeria.

Customer Service Agent (Remotely)

Sept, 2022 - Jan, 2024

- Answering questions about a company's products or services
- Processing orders and transactions
- Resolving issues and troubleshooting technical problems
- Delivering information about a company's offerings
- Providing proactive customer outreach
- Collecting and analyzing customer feedback

Education

YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

Herbert Macaulay Rd, Opp WAEC office, Yaba Lagos.

HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA: MICROBIOLOGY

CGPA: 3.06 (UPPER CREDIT)

Jan, 2020 - April, 2022.

YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

Herbert Macaulay Rd,
Opp WAEC office, Yaba Lagos.

NATIONAL DIPLOMA: SCIENCE LABORATORY

TECHNOLOGY

CGPA: 3.04 (UPPER CREDIT)

May, 2015 - October, 2018.

HELPERS INT'L COLLEGE SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE 13, Awe Street, Orile-Iganmu, Lagos, Nigeria.

Jan, 2008 - Jun, 2014.

Research Work

• Health Benefits of Momordica Charantia (Bitter Melon)

November, 2021.

Production of Herbal Tea from Ethnobotanical Plants

April, 2022.

Languages

- English, Fluent
- Yoruba, Fluent

Hobbies

- Coding
- Painting
- Research
- Listening to Music
- Reading

Certificate

Certified Web Professional - Web Developer

Sept, 2022.

National Youth Service Corps

2022 - 2023.